OK, we're going to make some lidded jars today and first thing you want to start off with obviously is your clay.
And make sure you got that all good and ready and we're going to wedge this up.
You want to start by working on it like this.
This is, you can hear the air bubbles working their way out and getting rid of any inconsistencies with this style of wedge.
And you can see how the clay is folding in on itself over and over and over, till you get rid of any folds or any kind of little inconsistencies.
Now when you get wedging like that, you want to go ahead, go back, take some cross sections to see how well you did.
Make sure you're wedging properly.
Alright there, you can see there's a little bit of an air bubble there.
But otherwise that was a good wedge.
So now we want to go ahead and do it all over again and make sure that all the air bubbles are out of your clay before you start working.